freeboh.com 2018-09-03

# Freeboh-Shift-based jobs in Singapore. Works for me!

At Freeboh, we understand that your privacy is important and we endeavour to protect your personal data. As used in this Privacy Policy, "personal data" means information such as: your name; mailing address; email address; telephone number; your location; identification/passport number; employment and educational history or any other personal data that may be supplied by you or collected about you as required by us. We hope that this Policy helps you to understand how we handle and use any personal data after collection. At Freeboh, we understand that your privacy is important and we endeavour to protect your personal information. As used in this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information such as: your name; mailing address; email address; telephone number; your location or other personal information that may be supplied by you or collected about you as required by us. We hope that this Policy helps you to understand how we handle and use any personal data after collection. 

  * Freeboh compiles this information into a statistical aggregate and uses this information for internal business and administrative purposes which includes improving our products and service offerings, and enhancing our customer service level. 
  * Freeboh will use your personal data from time to time to send you notices about special information, new programmes, and other similar information. 
  * Freeboh will disclose your personal data including but not limited to your name, contact number and relevant work and educational experience and work details to vendors of job listings to which you have placed a bid to. Apart from what we have set out in this Privacy Policy, Freeboh will not reveal your personal data to any other third-party unless required by law or court order. 
  * Freeboh does not sell, trade or rent your personal data to others. 
  * Freeboh understands and respects the privacy of individuals. Personal data is collected by Freeboh with your consent. The purpose for collecting, using and disclosing this information varies depending upon your request and will include:
    1. helping us to improve our service to you; 
    2. processing your application and/or registration and/or enquiry and any and all other ancillary administrative purposes; 
    3. the disclosure of your personal data to vendors of job listings to which you have placed a bid to; 
    4. informing you of upcoming events; 
    5. updating your records in our databases; monitoring and maintaining a copy of your record of previous job transactions (including all information arising from comments, reviews and messages posted by third-party individuals to your or relating to your account); 
    6. delivery and enhancement of our services under any contract which we may have with you; 
    7. planning the provision of new features; 
    8. monitoring and enhancing the provision of new features; 
    9. audit and other regulatory purposes and 
    10. publicity and marketing materials; 
    11. purposes incidental to each or all of the above. 

### Google login/Facebook Connect

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Google login or Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal data with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Such services give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

When you provide information from your social media profile, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our applications or websites, and (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly with the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

When you post information on public forums or similar functions at our Services, or when you interact with our Services through social networking sites (depending on your privacy settings), social media plug-ins or similar applications, this information could be seen by anyone on the Internet. Therefore, we cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social networking sites. For more information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how social networking sites handle your personal data, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies and terms of use.

If you delete your profile from a third-party service, such as Google or Facebook, information that has been shared with Freeboh from that service may still be retained by Freeboh . If you do not wish for us to retain such information, please [contact us](mailto:contact_us@Freeboh.com).

### Use of cookies

Freeboh uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Freeboh on our servers. Freeboh will use this information for the purpose of providing location relevant information to you and for user session management. Freeboh may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Freeboh's behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Freeboh in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

#### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

### Location information

Freeboh offers a variety of location-aware products and services to provide you with more relevant content for where you are in the world. We obtain information about your location through various methods like pinpointed GPS data or when you submit a partial address to look at a map of an area.

You must first provide permission through your device, browser or with Freeboh directly, before Freeboh obtains pinpointed physical location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity. Freeboh is not able to control the sharing of such information directly. Instead, you are able to withdraw your permission for Freeboh to access pinpointed location information through your web browser permissions.

When your web browser or email application requests a web page or email from another computer on the Internet, it automatically sends that computer the address where it should reply with the information requested. This is your computer's "IP address" (IP stands for "Internet protocol"). Depending on how you connect to the Internet through your Internet Service Provider (ISP), the IP address assigned to your computer may be different every time you log on. Freeboh may derive information about where your device is generally located based on your IP Address.

### Use of diary

Freeboh provides a diary feature to make the scheduling process even easier and more efficient. The information in your diary which arise from your use of Freeboh's services is stored on Freeboh's servers. When logged in using your Google account, Freeboh will also access Google calendar information associated with your account. Such information are displayed alongside your Freeboh data but are not stored on Freeboh's servers. Freeboh may also access publicly available calendar information for displaying significant public events, such as public holidays.

### Information about others/inviting friends

You can also submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to share content or recommendations. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. Some of our Services also allow you to invite your friends to join our services and to connect with you through social media features. Inviting friends is always optional. To do so, you may provide their contact information or may enter your log-in credentials to import email addresses from your address book from other sites that support such functionality (e.g., Google mail). You select the friends you want to invite to share in this experience.

While the supply of the information by you is voluntary, if you cannot provide or do not wish to provide the information sought, Freeboh may be unable to meet the purposes for which the information was collected.

Although every reasonable effort has been made to ensure that all personal data will be so protected, Freeboh cannot be responsible for any unauthorised use or misuse of such information and from risks which are inherent in all internet communications.

Freeboh reserves the right to change this Policy with or without notice from time to time.

If you have any questions on our Privacy Policy, please contact Freeboh's Data Protection Officer ("DPO") at [dpo@freeboh.com](mailto:dpo@freeboh.com).
